RG 062:166, Town of Wolcott
Connecticut State Library
Town of Wolcott records
1760-1915
Connecticut State Library
Wolcott (Conn.)
7 cubic feet
Administrative, election, court, land, school and tax records for the town of Wolcott.
RG062_166
T000602
Historical Note
The town of Wolcott was incorporated in May 1796 and was taken from Waterbury and Southington.
Scope and Content
Administrative, election, court, land, school and tax records for the town of Wolcott.
Index Terms
Alternate Creators:
Connecticut. Justice of the Peace (Wolcott)
Subjects:
Probate records -- Connecticut -- Wolcott; Voting registers -- Connecticut -- Wolcott; Elections -- Connecticut -- Wolcott -- Statistics; Voting -- Connecticut -- Wolcott -- Statistics; Justices of the peace -- Connecticut -- Wolcott; Writs -- Connecticut -- Wolcott; School enrollment -- Connecticut -- Wolcott -- Statistics; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Wolcott -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Wolcott -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Wolcott -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Wolcott -- Registers
Places:
Wolcott (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence; Wolcott (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1760-1915
  - Town and school meeting warnings and minutes, 1866-1900 (Box Box 1)
  - Appointments and resignations of town officials, 1909-1913 (Box Box 1)
  - Vital record abstracts, 1848-1897 (Box Box 1)
  - Vital and probate records, 1842-1890 (Box Box 1)
  - Registry lists, 1853-1905 (Box Box 2)
  - Election returns, printed ballots, 1833-1906, undated (Box Box 3)
  - Road and turnpike records, 1760-1828 (Box Box 4)
  - Writs of attachment, 1872-1906 (Box Box 4)
  - Deeds, 1814-1901 (Box Box 4)
  - Dog registers, 1878-1915 (Box Box 5)
  - Hunting license stubs, 1911-1914 (Box Box 5)
  - School register, 1874-1875 (Box Box 6)
  - School returns and financial records, circa 1851-1856 (Box Box 6)
  - Treasurers' records, 1797-1898 (Box Box 6)
  - Appointments of overseers and conservators, 1820-1900 (Box Box 6)
  - Orders for payment, 1871-1880 (Box Box 6)
  - Tax abstracts, 1797-1820 (Box Box 7)
    scattered
  - Grand lists, 1854-1900 (Box Box 7)
  - Justice Court records, circa 1800-1900 (Box Boxes 8-14)